Once I've figured out which metrics have significant changes, what comes next?
一旦得知了哪些指标发生了重要改变 接下来要做什么呢？
>> Well, now you have to decide what your results do and don't tell you.
现在你必须决定 结果会或者不会告诉你什么
If you have statistically significant results,
如果结果有统计意义
then that means that you're unlikely to have zero impact on the user experience.
意味着不太可能对用户体验没有影响
But now the questions come down to A, do you understand the change?
但是 现在问题变为 A 你了解这个变化吗？
And B, do you want to launch the change?
B 你想发布这些改变吗？
Okay, so what if I have a statistically significant change in some metrics but
如果一些指标中 在统计时有重大变化
then in others, I don't.
但是在其他指标中没有 那会怎样
Well, that goes back to A, do you understand the change?
那又回到问题 A 你了解这个变化吗？
And having intuition and
有直觉和许多其他实验的经验
experience with lots of other experiments can really help here.
能在这里给你提供帮助
For example, maybe you know that for small changes,
例如 你可能知道 对于一些小的变化
a change in one metric but no change all the other metrics is perfectly fine.
一个指标中的一个变化 但是在其他指标中没有变化是最完美的
But if you were to see those same results for a big change,
但是 如果你看见一个大变化的同样结果
that would probably indicate that there's something going wrong.
那可能表明有些东西出了问题
>> Okay, and the same question for slices.
同样一个小问题
What if your change has a positive impact on one slice of your users, but
假设你的变化对一小部分用户有积极影响
then, for another slice, there's no impact or there's a negative impact?
但是对其他用户没有影响或者有负面影响 那会如何？
>> Again, do you understand why?
你知道为什么吗？
Is it a question about having different users, and
这是一个关于有不同用户的问题吗
how much they like or don't like the change?
他们有多喜欢或者不喜欢这种变化？
Have you seen that effect in other experiments?
你在其他实验中见过那些影响吗？
Do you have a bug?
有 bug 吗？
These are all possibilities when you have changes
这些都是有可能的 当你有变化时
in one slice versus another.
在一些用户和其他用户间
Let me give you an example.
举个例子
Bolding, right,
粗体
we like to basically bold certain words in order to give them emphasis.
我们喜欢把某些词加粗来强调
Now, bolding in like English or German, or those types of alphabets,
现在 加粗英文或者德文等类型的字母
works really well for providing emphasis.
强调效果非常好
But if you try and bold in Japanese, or Korean, or Chinese,
但是如果加粗日文、韩文或者中文
a bolded character is actually really hard to read.
会使它们变得难以阅读
And it actually makes it harder for
也会增加用户的阅读难度
a user to read the word than if it was not bolded.
比起在没有加粗之前
And so in that situation,
在那种情况下
you may actually want to want something different for that slice.
你可能会想为那一部分用户做些不一样的事
Maybe use a different color as opposed to doing a bold.
不用加粗字体 可以使用不同的颜色
>> That makes sense.
那个很有意义
And then, bottom line, how do you decide whether to launch your change or not?
回归正题 如何决定是否发布改变？
>> You really have to ask yourself a few questions.
你必须问你自己几个问题
One, do I have statistically significant and
首先 有没有统计学意义上的和实际意义上的结果
practically significant results in order to justify the change?
证明这些变化有道理
The second question is, do I understand what that change has actually done with
第二个问题 我是否了解那些变化实际上
regards to user experience?
对用户体验有什么影响？
And the third one is, is it worth it?
第三个问题 它是否值得？
Now the key thing to remember is that the end goal is
关键的一点
actually making that recommendation that shows your judgment.
终极目标是给出表示你判断的建议
It's not about designing the experiment and running it and
它无关设计实验和进行实验
sizing it properly, and having all of the metric chosen correctly,
合理控制尺寸 正确选择所有指标
and all those different things.
和所有不同的东西
Those are all signposts towards your end goal of actually making
这些都是通向提建议这个终极目标
a recommendation.
的指路牌
And what's going to be remembered is,
需要记住的是
did you recommend to launch it or not and was it the right recommendation?
你是否建议发布它 是否是正确的建议？